(綱手)
で ナルトの修業は どうなってる？
So...
How is Naruto's training going?
(サクラ)はい。 カカシ先生が言うには➡
Well, according to Kakashi Sensei,
何か コツをつかんだらしくて。
it seems like he got a hold
of something.
完成までには もう少しかかる
って言ってました。
He said it's gonna take
a little longer to complete...
そうか…。
I see...
第十班に
カカシ先生が入ったっていうことは➡
Now that Kakashi Sensei
has joined Team Ten,
彼らと連係のとりやすい 第七班➡
Team Seven...our team,
should support them
つまり 私たちの小隊が
増援にいくべきだと➡
because of our close alliance
with them...right?
そういうことですよね？
察しがいいな。 さすが お前だ。
You're sharp...just as expected...
(シズネ)しかし ナルト君の新術が➡
But, we don't know when
Naruto will complete his new Jutsu.
いつ 完成するのかも
わかりませんし➡
別の小隊を向かわせたほうが…。
Wouldn't it be better to
send another team?
サクラ！ ヤマトに伝えろ。
Sakura!
Tell Yamato...
あと24時間で➡
To have Naruto complete
his new Jutsu in 24 hours!
ナルトの新術を完成させろ。
できない場合 別の小隊を➡
If not, I will send another team
as reinforcements!
増援に向かわせる とな。
はい。
Yes!
シズネ…
間に合わなかった場合を考えて➡
Shizune, look at the schedule
スケジュールを見て
第十班と連係のとれる➡
and put together a list of teams
that can go support Team Ten
小隊の編成案を出せ。
in case Naruto does not
complete it in time.
わかりました。
I got it.
さて… これからだ。
So, it's starting.
(カカシ)シカマル。
まず お前の作戦を聞こう。
Shikamaru... Let's hear your plan first.
(シカマル)カカシ先生が入ったことで➡
Now that you have joined,
I want to change the plan a bit.
少し作戦を変更したいんですけど。
(カカシ)わかった 説明してくれ。
I got it.
Please explain.
(シカマル)
いくつかのパターンにわけて説明する。
I will explain by dividing it
into several scenarios.
全員 しっかり
頭に 叩き込んでおいてくれよ。
Make sure all of you listen carefully.
Target: Locked On
(ナルト)
えっ？ カカシ先生たちが 暁を？
Huh? Kakashi Sensei and
the others went after the Akatsuki?
(サクラ)つい さっきのことよ。
They just left a minute ago...
(ヤマト)そうか… で 綱手様は何と？
I see...
So what did Lady Tsunade say?
私たちが増援にいくのがベストだと。
She said it's best that
we go to support them...
でも そのためには
早急に ナルトの新術を➡
But she also said that in order to do so,
we must complete
Naruto's new Jutsu immediately.
完成させる必要がある
って言われたわ。
ん… オレの新術を？
Huh?!
My new Jutsu?
24時間以内に
完成しなかった場合は➡
If you don't complete it within 24 hours,
別の小隊が
増援に向かうことになるわ。
then she's going to send
another team.
(ヤマト)24時間か…。
Within 24 hours, huh...
ナルト？
Naruto...?
あっ それは食べないほうが…。
Oh!
You shouldn't eat that...!
えっ…。
Huh?!
ナルト…。
Naruto...
さぁ ヤマト隊長➡
Captain Yamato,
let's start the training!
修業を始めるってばよ！
(シカマル)じゃあ カカシ先生 これ。
Kakashi Sensei, take this...
隙をみて 使ってください。
please use it
when there's an opening.
渡しておきます。
I'll let you keep it.
わかった。
しかし たった一度の接触で➡
I got it.
I'm impressed at how much you
observed about your opponent
敵を よく研究したね。
(シカマル)ただ もう一人の能力は➡
from just one encounter.
But the other one's power
is still unknown...
未知数が多くて。
《その上 入ったばかりのオレに
合わせて➡
On top of that, you've readjusted
the plan to fit the new member...
すぐに 作戦を再構築するとはね。
大したヤツだ》
It's remarkable.
限られた情報のなかで
立案できる作戦は 以上だ。
That's the plan I developed with
the limited information I had.
作戦を頭に入れたら➡
After you memorize the plans,
simulate them in your head
three times or more.
シミュレーションを頭の中で
３回以上やっといてくれ。
イメージトレーニングをやる やらないじゃ
作戦成功率が まるで違うからな。
The success rate of
the plan highly depends
on whether or not
you do image training.
(チョウジ)うん！
(いの)オッケー！
Yes.
Okay!
Okay, let's go.
(カカシ)よし！ 行くか。
はい。
Yes!
まずは ヤツらの痕跡を探さねえと。
First, we need to find their trail.
痕跡… あっ そうか！
Trail...
I get it, you're saying we need
to find the path
火ノ寺から 換金所へ向かう
道のりを 探そうっていうんだね。
between the Temple of Fire
and the Collection Office.
そこに残ってる 足跡や
ニオイを見つけるってことね。
You're saying we're going to find
their footsteps and scent there.
Well, I don't think that will be easy...
まっ 簡単に見つかるとは
思えねえけどな。
それじゃ 急ぐよ。
(いの)はい！
Let's hurry.
-Yeah.
-Yes.
(ペイン)
これで 二尾の封印は完了した。
The sealing of the Two-Tails
is now complete...
残りは あと四匹。
There are now only four remaining...
You are dismissed.
解散だ。
(飛段)ふぅ… やっとかよ！
(角都)木ノ葉へ行くぞ 飛段。
Finally!
We're going to
Hidden Leaf Village, Hidan.
Hidden Leaf Village...?
(デイダラ)木ノ葉だって？
Kakuzu, Hidan, if you are going
to Hidden Leaf Village,
(デイダラ)角都！ 飛段！
お前ら 木ノ葉へ行くんなら➡
I will give you one warning...yes.
一つ忠告しとくぜ。
There's a guy named Naruto Uzumaki
who's a Jinchuriki.
あそこには うずまき ナルトって
人柱力がいる。
ソイツにあったら
気をつけるこったな。
If you see him
you should be careful...yes.
(飛段)おい おいおい！
Hey hey hey!
Don't assume I'm the same as you,
Mr. Deidara!
テメエと一緒にするんじゃねえよ！
デイダラちゃんよ！
角都に 腕くっつけてもらった
若輩もんが！
You are the wuss who got his arms
sewed back on by Kakuzu!
(角都)首よりは マシだ。
It's better than his head...
って おい！ コラッ 角都！
Hey! Hey, Kakuzu!
Who's side are you on?!
テメエは どっちの味方だ！
Aren't we teammates?
(飛段)オレと お前は
連れ同士じゃねえのかよ！
そんなんだから テメエは！
(角都)黙れ！ 飛段！
- That's why you--!
- Shut up Hidan!
(角都)いいから 行くぞ！
Let's just go.
(飛段)チッ！
(飛段)うっ… あぁ…。
(飛段)
３日も じっとしてたからな。
I had to sit still for three days,
I'm going to go crazy...
暴れまくってやるぜ！
待ってろ！ 賞金首！ うん？
Wait for me, bounty.
おい 角都 どこへ行く？
換金所は こっちだろうが！
Hey, where are you going, Kakuzu?
The Collection Office is this way!
お前は バカか？
Are you stupid?
What?!
なんだと!?
(角都)オレたちの目的は人柱力だ。
Our target is the Jinchuriki.
わざわざ 戻ると
言った場所へ行って➡
There is no need to go back to
that place just to run into an ambush.
待ち伏せをくらう必要はない。
(角都)別のルートを通って
木ノ葉へ向かう。
Let's take a different route to
the Hidden Leaf Village.
あれから ３日たった。
It has been three days.
あの賞金首も 今頃は
木ノ葉に回収されてる。
The Hidden Leaf Village should have
retrieved that bounty by now.
ふん… まぁ そりゃそうだな。
Well, that's right.
そういえば…。
Oh yeah...
What?!
なんだよ!?
その 治りかけの傷
みっともない。 これで隠しとけ。
That scar is embarrassing.
Cover it up with this!
Hey!
This is my Headband.
おっ！ オレの額当てじゃねえか。
なんだ… わざわざ
拾っといてくれたのか？
Oh, you actually picked it up for me...?
角都 お前 結構
いいとこあんじゃねえか。
Kakuzu! You're pretty nice!
黙れ 飛段。 とっとと行くぞ。
Shut up Hidan!
Hurry, let's go!
あっ… おい！
ちょっと待てって！ おい 角都！
Oh! Hey! Wait a sec!
Hey! Kakuzu!
(飛段)お前 ホントは オレのこと
結構 好きだろ？ えっ？
Tell me the truth, you like me, right?
(角都)それ以上
何か言ったら殺すぞ。
If you keep talking,
I am going to kill you.
(飛段)ハハハ！
そんなに照れるなって。
Don't be shy...
やはり あの雨で
痕跡は見当たらないね。
As expected, the trail can't be
found due to the rain.
(カカシ)さて… どうしますか？
So, what are we going to do?
いずれにせよ 敵を見つけなきゃ
話になりませんからね。
Either way, we can't do anything
unless we find our enemy.
確か アイツら…。
I remember they said...
((チッ…。
We'll be right back...
Be prepared!
また すぐに戻る。
覚悟はしておけ。
(テメエら！ オレらが戻ってくるまで
じっとしてろ!!))
Stay still until we get back!
…って言ってたはず。
But obviously, they won't return
to the same place.
でも さすがに
同じ場所には戻らないよね。
換金所には ２小隊が
見張りについてるはずだけど…。
The second team should be
monitoring the Collection Office...
あの よく吠えるほうだけなら
ともかく もう１人いるからな。
The one that yells a lot is fine,
but there's the other guy...
別ルートをとってくるだろうが
ヤツらの目的地は ひとつ。
I bet they will use a different route,
but they have only one destination.
賞金目当てに
アスマの遺体を狙うにせよ➡
Whether they are going after
Asuma's corpse for money
人柱力のナルトが標的にせよ
向かう先は 木ノ葉だ。
or they are after Naruto,
their destination is Hidden Leaf Village!
…ってことは
広範囲の探索になるな。
Then that means, it'll be a wide search...
どうやって捜す？
How are we going to find them?
あれでいきます。
We'll go with that.
Huh?!
了解！
Got it.
《見つけた！》
I found them.
《いの : 間違いない…
まっすぐ木ノ葉に向かってる》
There's no mistake...they're headed
straight to Hidden Leaf Village.
《マズイ！》
Shoot!
あっ！
大丈夫？ いの。
Are you all right, Ino?!
ハァー 危なかった。
気づかれたのか？
That was close!
Did they notice?!
たぶん 大丈夫だと思う。
I think it's okay.
やっぱりヤツら
別ルートで木ノ葉に向かってる。
As expected, they're headed to
Hidden Leaf Village through a different route.
ここから２時の方向。
10分でぶつかる。
They're in the 2 o'clock direction.
We will run into them in ten minutes.
どうした 角都。
What happened, Kakuzu?!
いや なんでもない。
Naw, nothing...
気のせいだ。
チッ。 だったら急ぐぜ。
It's just my imagination...
Then let's hurry.
ああ。
Yeah...
よし 行こう。
All right. Let's go!
飛段。
ああ。
- Hidan...
- Yeah...
クソッ！
起爆札か！
- Damn it!
- It's a Paper Bomb!
角都！
腕を 硬化した。 ケガはない！
Kakuzu!
I hardened my arm.
I'm not injured.
それより影には気をつけておけ。
Forget that, watch out for the shadow...
ヘッ 何度も同じ手をくらうかよ！
I won't fall for it twice!
飛段 上だ！
Hidan, look up!
《また 起爆札！》
It's another Paper Bomb!
(角都)飛段 かわせ！
Hidan, dodge it!
くっ！
It didn't explode?!
《起爆しない》
They got us...
やられたな。
フン。
影真似手裏剣の術 成功。
Shadow Possession Shuriken Jutsu...
A success.
《動かねえ…》
I can't move.
ヤロー 影からは
逃げたのにどうやって。
You bastard... I dodged the shadow,
so how did you...
オレが投げたソイツは チャクラ刀だ。
The thing I threw is a Chakra Blade.
I bet you know that it's made
from a special metal
(シカマル)知ってんだろうが ソイツは
使用者のチャクラ性質を吸収する➡
特別な金属でできてる。
that absorbs the user's Chakra characteristics.
Kakuzu, what is he saying?
角都 何言ってんだ コイツ。
バカ 黙れ 飛段。
チッ。
Idiot! Shut up, Hidan.
(シカマル)吸収した チャクラによって➡
Due to the Chakra absorbed,
使用者の術に基づく
効果を発揮する。
it exhibits power based
on the user's Jutsu.
要は チャクラ刀自体がオレの
影真似の術を発動中ってことだ。
Basically, the Chakra Blade itself
is exhibiting my Shadow Possession Jutsu.
そのチャクラ刀は
アンタらにやられた アスマの形見だ。
That Chakra Blade is a memento
of Asuma, the man you killed.
あっ？
3,500万両か。
35 million ryo, huh...?
《アスマ…》
Asuma...
((アスマ : 木ノ葉の忍を
駒にたとえるなら➡
If I were to equate
Hidden Leaf Ninja to Shogi pieces,
シカマル… さしずめ お前は桂馬だな。
Shikamaru...
In the end, you would be a knight.
なんで？
Why?
Although weak in strength,
a knight can advance
力は弱いが 駒を飛び越して
進むことができる。
by jumping over pieces...
Its unique movement resembles
your flexible thinking.
(このユニークな動きは 型にはまらない
お前の柔軟な思考に似てる))
《なるほど…
この起爆札は フェイク… 紙きれか。
I see...
This Paper Bomb is a fake.
It's just paper...
コイツの狙いは ハナから
この チャクラ刀。
His aim was this Chakra Blade
from the beginning...
そのため
最初の起爆札つきのクナイは➡
Because of that, the first Kunai Knife
with the Paper Bomb
was a diversion to ensure that
we'd dodge the second Chakra Blade.
二度目のチャクラ刀を 確実にかわして
よけさせるための伏線。
そのうえで 影で オレたちの注意を
足元に引きつけたのは➡
Furthermore,
he used his shadow...
to make us focus
our attention on our feet.
He did it to make us
realize his attack from above and
上からの攻撃を ギリギリで気づかせ
ギリギリで かわさせ➡
make us dodge it at the last minute
オレたちの影を確実に射るため…。
in order to ensure that
he could grab hold of our shadows.
He's pretty clever.
コイツ… かなりの切れ者》
さてと… 仕上げといくか。
Well, let's finish this.
おい！ なに 黙りこんでんだよ
さっきから！
Hey!
Why the hell have you been so quiet?!
テメエまで捕まって
どうすんだよ！ 角都！
What are you doing getting caught, too?!
おいおい こりゃ はっきり言って
まずいんじゃねえのか!?
Hey! Hey! Hey!
To tell the truth, aren't we pretty screwed?!
まずい？ オレの計算じゃ➡
Screwed?
According to my plan,
it was finished
from the moment I caught you.
この手順で
お前らを捕まえた時点で終わりだ。
《うまくやったな》
You did a good job...
You bastard...
ヤロー…！
Damn it!
What are you doing?!
クソ！ 何を始める気だ!?
ハッ！ 一度 ミスったことを
二度 ミスるわけにはいかねぇしな。
There's no way I'm gonna miss
the second time.
これから テメエらを
雪隠詰めにすんのさ！
I'm going to corner you guys.
You jerks went after us
in the wrong order.
((テメエら
狙う順番を間違えたな))
今度は 狙う順番を
間違えねえからよ。
I'm not going to mess up
the order this time.
クソ…！
Damn it!
(飛段)テメエの顔は 覚えたぜ。
I know your face now!
オレが どうなろうと
絶対ぶっ殺す！
No matter what happens to me,
I'm gonna kill you.
お前 頭悪いだろ？
チッ！
You're stupid, aren't you?
角都 かわせ！
Kakuzu! Dodge it!
よっしゃあ!!
All right!
《どういうこと!?》
What's happening?
《まさか 本体から離れた腕が
単独で動くとはな…。
I didn't expect his arm to
move on its own
after being separated
from his body...
だが いつの間に？
But when did this happen?
はっ 起爆札で 攻撃した
あのときか！
It was when
I attacked with the paper bomb!
煙にまぎれて 右腕を地面に…。
While he was in the smoke,
he put this right arm in the ground...
チッ… さすがに暁。
Just what I'd expect
of the Akatsuki.
They all use insane abilities!
いずれも
変わった能力者揃いだぜ》
(角都)
終わりだと言ってはいても➡
You said we were finished,
オレの能力は
お前にとっては未知数…。
ならば きちんと距離をとって
次の手を仕掛ける。
オレの連れと違って 賢い。
だが 戦闘中に
分析ばかりしていても➡
すべてが計算どおりに
いくもんじゃない。
チッ。
ヘヘヘ… あ？
角都！ 連れと違いってのは
いったい どういう意味だよ！
そのものずばりだ バカ。
クソッ 体が！
角都 なんとかしろ!!
力押しとはな。
うっ しまった！
《今だ チョウジ！》
(チョウジ)肉弾針戦車！
(飛段)角都!!
(イビキ)さてと… これからアンタの
罪状認否をとる。
まずは アンタのことを
聞かせてもらおう。
(イビキ)それと アンタが接触していた
この男。
この男のことを話してもらう。
フンッ チクりは やらねえ。
なら 話してもらうのは やめだ。
オレのやり方で 吐かせてやる。
あ!!